<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vibe Vault</string>
    <string name="search_screen_help">Drag up the search panel to search. \n\ \n\ You can search individually in the artist and show description fields, or you can search them both at the same time.  You can add date restrictions to further refine your search. \n\ \n\ Hit the magnifying glass button to search. \n\ If you have results, you can hit the more results button for more. \n\ Hit the settings button for more search options.</string>
    <string name="home_screen_help">Developed by Andrew Pearson and Sanders DeNardi \n\ \u00a9 Copyright 2011.</string>
    <string name="show_details_screen_help">This screen lists all of the songs for whichever show was selected.  You have a few options with what you can do here... \n\ \n\ If you want to just play a song, click on it.  It will start playing in the background.  Playing a song will take you to the "Now Playing" screen.  You can also get there by dragging down from the status bar, or selected "Now Playing" from the menu after clicking the menu button.  The entire show will be queued to play if you click on a song.. \n\ \n\ If you want to download a song, long-press on the song, and you will have the option to do so.  You can even choose to download the entire show!  If a song is downloaded, a star will appear next to it, and it will play from your phone (instead of from the Internet) if you click on it.  You can also play it by going to "Downloaded Songs" from the home screen. \n\ \n\ If you want to reccomend a song to a friend, long-press on the song and you will have the option to do so.</string>
	<string name="download_screen_help">Active Downloads shows you the status of songs that you have (or are) downloading in this Vibe Vault session. \n\ \n\ Shows Downloaded gives you a list of shows from which you\'ve downloaded songs.  Click a show to see what songs you\'ve downloaded from it.  Click a song to start playing it immediately (and queue up the whole show), or long-press on a song to add it to the current PlayList.</string>
	<string name="now_playing_screen_help">Use the playback controls at the top of the screen to manage your now playing list.  Grab the icon on the left side of the song to move it.  Sliding it to the right will delete it (you can also accomplish this by long-pressing on the song).  The currently playing song is in yellow text. \n\ \n\ Drag up the PlayList bar at the bottom of the screen.  You can save the current PlayList, delete PlayLists, load old PlayLists, etc.</string>
	<string name="recent_shows_screen_help">A list of recently viewed shows.  Click one to open it up.</string>
	<string name="downloaded_show_screen_help">Click on a song to start playing it immediately (and queue up the rest of the show), or long-press on a song to add it to the current PlayList.</string>
	<string name="browse_artists_screen_help">The first time that you open this screen, Vibe Vault will automatically fetch a list of every artist available and the number of shows that they respectively have which are available.  After that, simply clicking on a letter will show the artists whose name begins with that letter.  Clicking on the artist will bring up the Search Screen, populated with that artist.</string>
	<string-array name="date_modifier">
		<item>Before</item>
		<item>After</item>
		<item>In Year</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>